[
     {
      "Question": "Rob just got a new car, and he wants to ride it to the top of a mountain and visit a lookout point. If he drives 10470 meters along a road that is inclined 6 degrees to the horizontal, how high above his starting point is he when he arrives at the lookout?",
      "Answer": 1094.413
     },
     {
      "Question": "A man sits of a balcony next to a building at an unknown distance. The angle of elevation to the top is 30 degrees and the angle of depression to the bottom is 21 degrees, the height of the building above him is 173.205ft and the height of the building below him is 115.169 ft. What is the man's distance from the building?",
      "Answer": 300
     },
     {
      "Question": "While running his favorite cross-country course, Eddie reaches the hardest part, a hill that is 2500 feet long. The hill has an incline of 12 degrees. How much elevation did Eddie gain?",
      "Answer": 519.779
     },
     {
      "Question": "If a treadmill is 48 inches long and the front is 8.335 inches higher than the back of the treadmill. What angle is the treadmill inclined at?",
      "Answer": 10
     },
     {
      "Question": "A plane has travelled 32 miles on an unknown heading. The plane has travelled 21 miles north. What heading east of north is the plane heading?",
      "Answer": 41.014
     },
     {
      "Question": "A semi-driver wants to know the angle of elevation of a ramp. They know it is 115 feet long and 10 feet high. What is the angle of elevation of the ramp?",
      "Answer": 4.97
     },
     {
      "Question": "While waiting for your sister to finish her bungee jump, you decide to figure out how you are from the platform. You know the platform is 341ft tall and the angle of elevation from you to the top of the platform is 80 degrees. How far from the platform are you?",
      "Answer": 60.128
     },
     {
      "Question": "While running his favorite cross-country course, Eddie reaches the hardest part, a hill that is 3150 feet long. The hill has an incline of 13 degrees. How much elevation did Eddie gain?",
      "Answer": 708.596
     },
     {
      "Question": "While waiting for your sister to finish her bungee jump, you decide to figure out the angle of elevation to the top of the platform. You know the platform is 192ft tall and you are 251ft from the platform. What is the angle of elevation to the platform?",
      "Answer": 37.414
     },
     {
      "Question": "SImon bought a new shop and wants to order a sign for the roof. From where he stands, the distance to the building is 41 feet. The height from the top of the sign is 29 feet. What is the angle of elevation to the top of the sign?",
      "Answer": 54.728
     },
     {
      "Question": "Pacing off 123 ft. on flat ground from the base of a tree, a forester measures the\nangle of elevation to the top of the tree as 60 degrees. What is the height of the tree?\n",
      "Answer": 213.042
     },
     {
      "Question": "Clare is playing her favorite game of baseball while she hits a ball straight into the dirt. She hit the ball with an angle of depression of 6 degrees and the ball hit the dirt 54 feet away from her. How high above the home plate was the ball when hit?",
      "Answer": 5.676
     },
     {
      "Question": "From the top of lighthouse, the distance to a boat is 351 meters. If the angle of depression to the boat is 16 degrees, what is the height of the lighthouse above the sea?",
      "Answer": 97
     },
     {
      "Question": "SImon bought a new shop and wants to order a sign for the roof. From where he stands, the distance to the building is 32 feet. The height from the top of the sign is 24 feet. What is the angle of elevation to the top of the sign?",
      "Answer": 36.87
     },
     {
      "Question": "While running his favorite cross-country course, Eddie reaches the hardest part, a hill that has an incline of 6 degrees. Eddie gains 1300 feet in elevation at the top. What is the length of hill?",
      "Answer": 12436.804
     },
     {
      "Question": "A semi-driver wants to know the height of a ramp. They know it is 450 ft long and the angle of elevation is 8 degrees. What is the height of the ramp?",
      "Answer": 63.243
     },
     {
      "Question": "While running his favorite cross-country course, Eddie reaches the hardest part, a hill that is 4020 feet long. The hill has an incline of 18 degrees. How much elevation did Eddie gain?",
      "Answer": 1242.248
     },
     {
      "Question": "Clare is playing her favorite game of baseball while she hits a ball straight into the dirt. She hit the ball 5.5 feet above home plate and the ball hit the dirt 80 feet away from her. What was the angle of depression of the ball?",
      "Answer": 3.933
     },
     {
      "Question": "A man sits on a balcony next to a building 191 feet away. The angle of elevation to the top is 30 degrees and the angle of depression to the bottom is 9 degrees. How tall is the building?",
      "Answer": 140.525
     },
     {
      "Question": "A semi-driver wants to know the angle of elevation of a ramp. They know it is 90 feet long and 15 feet high. What is the angle of elevation of the ramp?",
      "Answer": 9.462
     },
     {
      "Question": "If a treadmill is 20 inches long and the front is 4 inches higher than the back of the treadmill. What angle is the treadmill inclined at?",
      "Answer": 11.537
     },
     {
      "Question": "SImon bought a new shop and wants to order a sign for the roof. From where he stands, the distance to the building is 42 feet. The height from the top of the sign is 42 feet. What is the angle of elevation to the top of the sign?",
      "Answer": 45
     },
     {
      "Question": "If the distance from the point directly below a helicopter to a landing pad is known to be 342ft and the angle of depression to the landing pad is 60 degrees, what is the current altitude of the helicopter?",
      "Answer": 197.454
     },
     {
      "Question": "SImon bought a new shop and wants to order a sign for the roof. From where he stands, the distance to the building is 33 feet. The height from the top of the sign is 32 feet. What is the angle of elevation to the top of the sign?",
      "Answer": 45.881
     },
     {
      "Question": "From the hay loft door, a farmer sees his dog on the ground. The farmer's eye level is 13.5 feet above the ground. The dog is 44 feet from the open barn door directly below the farmer. What is the angle of depression from the farmer to the dog?",
      "Answer": 17.057
     },
     {
      "Question": "On a windy day, a rope tightly secures a hot air balloon to a stake in the ground. From the balloon, the angle of depression to the stake is 62 degrees. The balloon is at a height of 79.465 feet. What is the length of the rope securing the balloon",
      "Answer": 90
     },
     {
      "Question": "A tree casts a shadow measuring 63ft with an angle of elevation to the sun of 74 degrees. Given this information, what is the height of the tree?",
      "Answer": 219.707
     },
     {
      "Question": "While waiting for your sister to finish her bungee jump, you decide to figure out how tall the platform she is jumping off is. You are standing 124ft from the base of the platform, and the angle of elevation from your position to the top of the platform is 65 degrees. How many feet tall is the platform?",
      "Answer": 265.919
     },
     {
      "Question": "A lifeguard is at the top of tower that is 12 feet tall. The base of the tower is 42 feet away from a swimmer in the pool. What is the angle of depression from the lifeguard to the swimmer?",
      "Answer": 15.945
     },
     {
      "Question": "While running his favorite cross-country course, Eddie reaches the hardest part, a hill that is 2400 feet long. The hill has an incline of 15 degrees. How much elevation did Eddie gain?",
      "Answer": 621.166
     },
     {
      "Question": "A lighthouse built at sea level is 35 meters tall. From a buoy the angle of elevation to the top of the lighthouse is 30 degrees. How far is the buoy from the foot of the lighthouse?",
      "Answer": 60.622
     },
     {
      "Question": "A semi-driver wants to know the angle of elevation of a ramp. They know it is 300 feet long and 30 feet high. What is the angle of elevation of the ramp?",
      "Answer": 5.711
     },
     {
      "Question": "On a windy day, a 49 foot rope tightly secures a hot air balloon to a stake in the ground. From the balloon, the angle of depression to the stake is 39 degrees. What is the height of the balloon",
      "Answer": 30.837
     },
     {
      "Question": "A helicopter that is 500ft in the air measures the angle of depression to a\nlanding pad as 30 degrees. How far is the landing pad from the point directly beneath the helicopterâ€™s current position on the ground?",
      "Answer": 288.675
     },
     {
      "Question": "Pacing off 100ft. on flat ground from the base of a tree which measures 100ft in height. What is the angle of elevation to the top of the tree?",
      "Answer": 45
     },
     {
      "Question": "Pacing off 225 ft. on flat ground from the base of a tree which measures 189ft in height. What is the angle of elevation to the top of the tree?",
      "Answer": 40
     },
     {
      "Question": "A tree casts a shadow measuring 270ft with an angle of elevation to the sun of 33 degrees. Given this information, what is the height of the tree?",
      "Answer": 176
     },
     {
      "Question": "On a windy day, a rope tightly secures a hot air balloon to a stake in the ground. From the balloon, the angle of depression to the stake is 39 degrees. The balloon is at a height of 85 feet. What is the length of the rope securing the balloon",
      "Answer": 135.066
     },
     {
      "Question": "A lighthouse built at sea level is 18 meters tall. The buoy is 85 meters from the base of the lighthouse. What is the angle of elevation from the buoy to the top of the lighthouse?",
      "Answer": 11.957
     },
     {
      "Question": "A plane has traveled 12 miles on a course heading 54 degrees east of north. How far north has the plane travelled at this point?",
      "Answer": 7.053
     },
     {
      "Question": "Pacing on flat ground from the base of a tree which measures 126ft in height. The angle of elevation from the observer to the top of the tree is 40 degrees. What is the distance of the observer from the tree?",
      "Answer": 150
     },
     {
      "Question": "A plane has traveled 52 miles on a course heading 47 degrees east of north. How far north has the plane travelled at this point?",
      "Answer": 35.464
     },
     {
      "Question": "Clare is playing her favorite game of baseball while she hits a ball straight into the dirt. She hit the ball with an angle of depression of 4 degrees and the ball hit the dirt 84 feet away from her. How high above the home plate was the ball when hit?",
      "Answer": 5.874
     },
     {
      "Question": "A lifeguard is at the top of tower that is 18 feet tall. The base of the tower is 61.177 feet away from a swimmer in the pool. What is the angle of depression from the lifeguard to the swimmer?",
      "Answer": 15
     },
     {
      "Question": "A man sits on a balcony next to a building 306 feet away. The angle of elevation to the top is 9 degrees and the angle of depression to the bottom is 41 degrees. How tall is the building?",
      "Answer": 314.467
     },
     {
      "Question": "Pacing on flat ground from the base of a tree which measures 147ft in height. If the angle of elevation from the observer to the top of the tree is 31 degrees, what is the distance of the observer from the tree?",
      "Answer": 244.649
     },
     {
      "Question": "While waiting for your sister to finish her bungee jump, you decide to figure out the angle of elevation to the top of the platform. You know the platform is 427ft tall and you are 78ft from the platform. What is the angle of elevation to the platform?",
      "Answer": 79.648
     },
     {
      "Question": "While waiting for your sister to finish her bungee jump, you decide to figure out how you are from the platform. You know the platform is 209ft tall and the angle of elevation from you to the top of the platform is 64 degrees. How far from the platform are you?",
      "Answer": 101.936
     },
     {
      "Question": "A man sits on a balcony next to a building 174 feet away. The angle of elevation to the top is 23 degrees and the angle of depression to the bottom is 10 degrees. How tall is the building?",
      "Answer": 104.539
     },
     {
      "Question": "If a treadmill is 24 inches long and the front is 5 inches higher than the back of the treadmill. What angle is the treadmill inclined at?",
      "Answer": 12.025
     },
     {
      "Question": "While waiting for your sister to finish her bungee jump, you decide to figure out how tall the platform she is jumping off is. You are standing 155 feet from the base of the platform, and the angle of elevation from your position to the top of the platform is 72 degrees. How many feet tall is the platform?",
      "Answer": 477.041
     },
     {
      "Question": "On a windy day, a 38 foot rope tightly secures a hot air balloon to a stake in the ground. From the balloon, the angle of depression to the stake is 52 degrees. What is the height of the balloon",
      "Answer": 29.944
     },
     {
      "Question": "A plane has traveled 20 miles on a course heading 33 degrees east of north. How far north has the plane travelled at this point?",
      "Answer": 16.773
     },
     {
      "Question": "Pacing on flat ground from the base of a tree which measures 122ft in height. If the angle of elevation from the observer to the top of the tree is 27 degrees, what is the distance of the observer from the tree?",
      "Answer": 239.438
     },
     {
      "Question": "Pacing off 176 ft. on flat ground from the base of a tree, a forester measures the\nangle of elevation to the top of the tree as 55â—¦. What is the height of the tree?\n",
      "Answer": 251.354
     },
     {
      "Question": "A lifeguard is at the top of tower that is 24 feet tall. The base of the tower is 52 feet away from a swimmer in the pool. What is the angle of depression from the lifeguard to the swimmer?",
      "Answer": 24.775
     },
     {
      "Question": "A helicopter that is 700ft in the air measures the angle of depression to a\nlanding pad as 20 degrees. How far is the landing pad from the point directly beneath the helicopterâ€™s current position on the ground?",
      "Answer": 254.779
     },
     {
      "Question": "A shadow cast by a tree measures 270ft long. If the tree has a known height of 176ft, what is angle of elevation to the sun?",
      "Answer": 33.02
     },
     {
      "Question": "A lighthouse built at sea level is 20 meters tall. The buoy is 100 meters from the base of the lighthouse. What is the angle of elevation from the buoy to the top of the lighthouse?",
      "Answer": 11.31
     },
     {
      "Question": "Sophie just got a new car, and she wants to ride it to the top of a mountain and visit a lookout point. She drives 14300 meters along a road and ends up 2900 meters above her starting point when she arrives at the lookout point. What is the angle of elevation of the road?",
      "Answer": 11.701
     },
     {
      "Question": "A helicopter that is 573ft in air. If the distance from the point on the ground directly below the helicopter to a landing pad is known to be 241ft, what is the angle of depression to the landing pad?",
      "Answer": 22.811
     },
     {
      "Question": "While running his favorite cross-country course, Eddie reaches the hardest part, a hill that has an incline of 8 degrees. Eddie gains 900 feet in elevation at the top. What is the length of hill?",
      "Answer": 6466.767
     },
     {
      "Question": "While waiting for your sister to finish her bungee jump, you decide to figure out how tall the platform she is jumping off is. You are standing 124ft from the base of the platform, and the angle of elevation from your position to the top of the platform is 72 degrees. How many feet tall is the platform?",
      "Answer": 361.633
     },
     {
      "Question": "Richard just got a new car, and he wants to ride it to the top of a mountain and visit a lookout point. He drives on a road inclined 24 degrees to the horizontal and ends up 5287.576 meters above his starting point when he arrives at the lookout point. What is the length of the road he drove on?",
      "Answer": 13000
     },
     {
      "Question": "From the top of a lighthouse that sits 140 meters above the sea, the distance to a boat is 231 meters. What is the angle of depression to the boat?",
      "Answer": 37.305
     },
     {
      "Question": "While running his favorite cross-country course, Eddie reaches the hardest part, a hill that is 3000 feet long. Eddie gains 776.5 feet in elevation at the top. What is the incline of the hill?",
      "Answer": 15
     },
     {
      "Question": "If the angle of depression from the top of a lighthouse with a height of 200 meters to a boat is 45 degrees, what is the distance to the boat?",
      "Answer": 282.843
     },
     {
      "Question": "From the hay loft door, a farmer sees his dog on the ground. The angle of depression to the dog is 37 degrees. The farmer's eye level is 15 feet above the ground. How many feet must the dog walk to reach the barn door directly below the farmer?",
      "Answer": 11.303
     },
     {
      "Question": "A plane has traveled 24 miles on a course heading 24 degrees east of north. How far north has the plane travelled at this point?",
      "Answer": 21.925
     },
     {
      "Question": "On a windy day, a rope tightly secures a hot air balloon to a stake in the ground. From the balloon, the angle of depression to the stake is 71 degrees. The balloon is at a height of 71 feet. What is the length of the rope securing the balloon",
      "Answer": 75.091
     },
     {
      "Question": "If a treadmill is 48 inches long and is set to an incline of 12 degrees, how much higher is the front of the treadmill than the back?",
      "Answer": 9.98
     },
     {
      "Question": "A 79ft tall tree casts a shadow of an unknown length. If the angle of elevation to the sun is 31 degrees, what is the length of the shadow?",
      "Answer": 131.478
     },
     {
      "Question": "While running his favorite cross-country course, Eddie reaches the hardest part, a hill that has an incline of 10 degrees. Eddie gains 1040 feet in elevation at the top. What is the length of hill?",
      "Answer": 5989.121
     },
     {
      "Question": "While running his favorite cross-country course, Eddie reaches the hardest part, a hill that is 3250 feet long. The hill has an incline of 11 degrees. How much elevation did Eddie gain?",
      "Answer": 620.129
     },
     {
      "Question": "Clare is playing her favorite game of baseball while she hits a ball straight into the dirt. She hit the ball 5 feet above home plate and the ball hit the dirt 52 feet away from her. What was the angle of depression of the ball?",
      "Answer": 5.492
     },
     {
      "Question": "A helicopter that is 450ft in the air measures the angle of depression to a\nlanding pad as 57 degrees. How far is the landing pad from the point directly beneath the helicopterâ€™s current position on the ground?\n",
      "Answer": 692.939
     },
     {
      "Question": "A man sits on a balcony next to a building 279 feet away. The angle of elevation to the top is 10 degrees and the angle of depression to the bottom is 25 degrees. How tall is the building?",
      "Answer": 179.295
     },
     {
      "Question": "A helicopter that is 200ft in the air measures the angle of depression to a\nlanding pad as 45 degrees. How far is the landing pad from the point directly beneath the helicopterâ€™s current position on the ground?",
      "Answer": 200
     },
     {
      "Question": "A helicopter that is 400ft in the air measures the angle of depression to a\nlanding pad as 40 degrees. How far is the landing pad from the point directly beneath the helicopterâ€™s current position on the ground?\n",
      "Answer": 353.64
     },
     {
      "Question": "A semi-driver wants to know the height of a ramp. They know it is 500 ft long and the angle of elevation is 10 degrees. What is the height of the ramp?",
      "Answer": 88.163
     },
     {
      "Question": "Rob just got a new car, and he wants to ride it to the top of a mountain and visit a lookout point. He drives 12300 meters along a road and ends up 2750 meters above his starting point when he arrives at the lookout point. What is the angle of elevation of the road?",
      "Answer": 12.919
     },
     {
      "Question": "A ladder 11 meters long makes an angle of 18 degrees with the side of a building. How far up the building does the ladder reach?",
      "Answer": 11.462
     },
     {
      "Question": "SImon bought a new shop and wants to order a sign for the roof. From where he stands, the angle of elevation to the top of the sign is 37 degrees and the angle of elevation to the bottom of the sign is 22 degrees. Simon is standing 35 feet from the building. How tall is the sign?",
      "Answer": 12.233
     },
     {
      "Question": "While waiting for your sister to finish her bungee jump, you decide to figure out the angle of elevation to the top of the platform. You know the platform is 154ft tall and you are 401ft from the platform. What is the angle of elevation to the platform?",
      "Answer": 21.009
     },
     {
      "Question": "A plane has travelled 30 miles on an unknown heading. The plane has travelled 18 miles north. What heading east of north is the plane heading?",
      "Answer": 36.87
     },
     {
      "Question": "While running his favorite cross-country course, Eddie reaches the hardest part, a hill that has an incline of 15 degrees. Eddie gains 776.5 feet in elevation at the top. What is the length of hill?",
      "Answer": 3000
     },
     {
      "Question": "A ladder 12 meters long makes an angle of 30 degrees with the side of a building. How far up the building does the ladder reach?",
      "Answer": 10.392
     },
     {
      "Question": "SImon bought a new shop and wants to order a sign for the roof. From where he stands, the distance to the building is 30 feet. The height from the top of the sign is 24 feet. What is the angle of elevation to the top of the sign?",
      "Answer": 51.34
     },
     {
      "Question": "A ladder reaches 14.5 meters up a building and makes an angle of 21 degrees with the side of the building. What is the length of the ladder?",
      "Answer": 15.532
     },
     {
      "Question": "While waiting for your sister to finish her bungee jump, you decide to figure out how you are from the platform. You know the platform is 198ft tall and the angle of elevation from you to the top of the platform is 37 degrees. How far from the platform are you?",
      "Answer": 262.755
     },
     {
      "Question": "While running his favorite cross-country course, Eddie reaches the hardest part, a hill that has an incline of 9 degrees. Eddie gains 1000 feet in elevation at the top. What is the length of hill?",
      "Answer": 6392.456
     },
     {
      "Question": "A plane has traveled 37 miles on a course heading 51 degrees east of north. How far north has the plane travelled at this point?",
      "Answer": 23.285
     },
     {
      "Question": "From the top of a lighthouse that sits 170 meters above the sea, the distance to a boat is 187 meters. What is the angle of depression to the boat?",
      "Answer": 65.38
     },
     {
      "Question": "A tree casts a shadow measuring 75ft with an angle of elevation to the sun of 45 degrees. Given this information, what is the height of the tree?",
      "Answer": 75
     },
     {
      "Question": "While running his favorite cross-country course, Eddie reaches the hardest part, a hill that is 3000 feet long. The hill has an incline of 15 degrees. How much elevation did Eddie gain?",
      "Answer": 776.457
     },
     {
      "Question": "A lighthouse built at sea level is 30 meters tall. From a buoy the angle of elevation to the top of the lighthouse is 40 degrees. How far is the buoy from the foot of the lighthouse?",
      "Answer": 35.753
     },
     {
      "Question": "SImon bought a new shop and wants to order a sign for the roof. From where he stands, the distance to the building is 31 feet. The height from the top of the sign is 26 feet. What is the angle of elevation to the top of the sign?",
      "Answer": 39.987
     },
     {
      "Question": "Riley just got a new car, and she wants to ride it to the top of a mountain and visit a lookout point. She drives 15000 meters along a road and ends up 3100 meters above her starting point when she arrives at the lookout point. What is the angle of elevation of the road?",
      "Answer": 11.927
     },
     {
      "Question": "A 142ft tall tree casts a shadow of an unknown length. If the angle of elevation to the sun is 60 degrees, what is the length of the shadow?",
      "Answer": 81.984
     },
     {
      "Question": "A lifeguard is at the top of tower that is 16 feet tall. The base of the tower is 10 feet away from a swimmer in the pool. What is the angle of depression from the lifeguard to the swimmer?",
      "Answer": 57.995
     },
     {
      "Question": "If a treadmill is 20 inches long and is set to an incline of 9 degrees, how much higher is the front of the treadmill than the back?",
      "Answer": 3.129
     },
     {
      "Question": "A man sits on a balcony next to a building 450 feet away. The angle of elevation to the top is 30 degrees and the angle of depression to the bottom is 21 degrees. How tall is the building?",
      "Answer": 576.728
     },
     {
      "Question": "A lifeguard is at the top of tower that is 15 feet tall. The base of the tower is 31 feet away from a swimmer in the pool. What is the angle of depression from the lifeguard to the swimmer?",
      "Answer": 25.821
     },
     {
      "Question": "A man sits on a balcony next to a building 194 feet away. The angle of elevation to the top is 26 degrees and the angle of depression to the bottom is 10 degrees. How tall is the building?",
      "Answer": 122.187
     },
     {
      "Question": "A 43ft tall tree casts a shadow of an unknown length. If the angle of elevation to the sun is 22 degrees, what is the length of the shadow?",
      "Answer": 106.429
     },
     {
      "Question": "From the top of a lighthouse that sits 120 meters above the sea, the angle of depression of a boat is 52. How far from the boat is the top of the lighthouse?",
      "Answer": 152.282
     },
     {
      "Question": "A semi-driver wants to know the angle of elevation of a ramp. They know it is 350 feet long and 40 feet high. What is the angle of elevation of the ramp?",
      "Answer": 7.017
     },
     {
      "Question": "A semi-driver wants to know the angle of elevation of a ramp. They know it is 325 feet long and 30 feet high. What is the angle of elevation of the ramp?",
      "Answer": 5.274
     },
     {
      "Question": "From the top of a lighthouse that sits 100 meters above the sea, the angle of depression of a boat is 30. How far from the boat is the top of the lighthouse?",
      "Answer": 200
     },
     {
      "Question": "If the distance from the point directly below a helicopter on the ground to a landing pad is known to be 373ft and the angle of depression to the landing pad is 25 degrees, what is the current altitude of the helicopter?",
      "Answer": 800
     },
     {
      "Question": "While waiting for your sister to finish her bungee jump, you decide to figure out the angle of elevation to the top of the platform. You know the platform is 321ft tall and you are 103ft from the platform. What is the angle of elevation to the platform?",
      "Answer": 72.21
     },
     {
      "Question": "While running his favorite cross-country course, Eddie reaches the hardest part, a hill that has an incline of 9 degrees. Eddie gains 1100 feet in elevation at the top. What is the length of hill?",
      "Answer": 7031.698
     },
     {
      "Question": "Clare is playing her favorite game of baseball while she hits a ball straight into the dirt. She hit the ball 6 feet above home plate and the ball hit the dirt 63 feet away from her. What was the angle of depression of the ball?",
      "Answer": 5.44
     },
     {
      "Question": "A 176ft tall tree casts a shadow that is 270ft long. What is the angle of elevation to the sun?",
      "Answer": 33.02
     },
     {
      "Question": "If a treadmill is 22 inches long and the front is 5.5 inches higher than the back of the treadmill. What angle is the treadmill inclined at?",
      "Answer": 14.478
     },
     {
      "Question": "Clare is playing her favorite game of baseball while she hits a ball straight into the dirt. She hit the ball with an angle of depression of 4.574 degrees and the ball hit the dirt 50 feet away from her. How high above the home plate was the ball when hit?",
      "Answer": 4
     },
     {
      "Question": "A ladder reaches 18.5 meters up a building and makes an angle of 11 degrees with the side of the building. What is the length of the ladder?",
      "Answer": 18.846
     },
     {
      "Question": "Eric just got a new car, and he wants to ride it to the top of a mountain and visit a lookout point. He drives 10400 meters along a road and ends up 1570 meters above his starting point when he arrives at the lookout point. What is the angle of elevation of the road?",
      "Answer": 8.683
     },
     {
      "Question": "If a treadmill is 40 inches long and the front is 4.5 inches higher than the back of the treadmill. What angle is the treadmill inclined at?",
      "Answer": 6.46
     },
     {
      "Question": "Clare just got a new car, and she wants to ride it to the top of a mountain and visit a lookout point. If she drives 9320 meters along a road that is inclined 12 degrees to the horizontal, how high above her starting point is she when she arrives at the lookout?",
      "Answer": 1937.737
     },
     {
      "Question": "Jarod just got a new car, and he wants to ride it to the top of a mountain and visit a lookout point. If he drives 13000 meters along a road that is inclined 24 degrees to the horizontal, how high above his starting point is he when he arrives at the lookout?",
      "Answer": 5287.576
     },
     {
      "Question": "A semi-driver wants to know the angle of elevation of a ramp. They know it is 400 feet long and 20 feet high. What is the angle of elevation of the ramp?",
      "Answer": 2.862
     },
     {
      "Question": "A lifeguard is at the top of tower that is 21 feet tall. The angle of depression from the lifeguard to a swimmer in the pool is 53 degrees. What is the distance from the base of the tower to the swimmer?",
      "Answer": 15.825
     },
     {
      "Question": "While waiting for your sister to finish her bungee jump, you decide to figure out how you are from the platform. You know the platform is 303ft tall and the angle of elevation from you to the top of the platform is 72 degrees. How far from the platform are you?",
      "Answer": 98.451
     },
     {
      "Question": "Given the height of a bungee jump platform is 477ft and you are currently 155ft from the base of the platform, what is the angle of elevation to the platform?",
      "Answer": 72
     },
     {
      "Question": "Pacing off 150 ft. on flat ground from the base of a tree, a forester measures the\nangle of elevation to the top of the tree as 40â—¦. What is the height of the tree?",
      "Answer": 125.865
     },
     {
      "Question": "A helicopter that is 1600ft in the air measures the angle of depression to a landing pad as 25 degrees. How far is the landing pad from the point directly beneath the helicopterâ€™s current position on the ground?\n",
      "Answer": 746.092
     },
     {
      "Question": "A helicopter is 242ft in the air. If the distance from the point on the ground directly below the helicopter to a landing pad is known to be 651ft, what is the angle of depression to the landing pad?",
      "Answer": 69.608
     },
     {
      "Question": "If a treadmill is 50 inches long and is set to an incline of 11 degrees, how much higher is the front of the treadmill than the back?",
      "Answer": 9.54
     },
     {
      "Question": "While waiting for your sister to finish her bungee jump, you decide to figure out how you are from the platform. You know the platform is 172ft tall and the angle of elevation from you to the top of the platform is 41 degrees. How far from the platform are you?",
      "Answer": 197.863
     },
     {
      "Question": "A lighthouse built at sea level is 25 meters tall. From a buoy the angle of elevation to the top of the lighthouse is 45 degrees. How far is the buoy from the foot of the lighthouse?",
      "Answer": 25
     },
     {
      "Question": "A lighthouse built at sea level is 50 meters tall. From a buoy the angle of elevation to the top of the lighthouse is 64 degrees. How far is the buoy from the foot of the lighthouse?",
      "Answer": 23.315
     },
     {
      "Question": "A semi-driver wants to know the height of a ramp. They know it is 300 ft long and the angle of elevation is 6 degrees. What is the height of the ramp?",
      "Answer": 31.531
     },
     {
      "Question": "A ladder reaches 19 meters up a building and makes an angle of 12 degrees with the side of the building. What is the length of the ladder?",
      "Answer": 19.424
     },
     {
      "Question": "A semi-driver wants to know the angle of elevation of a ramp. They know it is 150 feet long and 35 feet high. What is the angle of elevation of the ramp?",
      "Answer": 13.134
     },
     {
      "Question": "From the top of a lighthouse that sits 150 meters above the sea, the distance to a boat is 171 meters. What is the angle of depression to the boat?",
      "Answer": 61.306
     },
     {
      "Question": "A lifeguard is at the top of tower that is 19 feet tall. The angle of depression from the lifeguard to a swimmer in the pool is 42 degrees. What is the distance from the base of the tower to the swimmer?",
      "Answer": 21.102
     },
     {
      "Question": "Pacing on flat ground from the base of a tree which measures 100ft in height. If the angle of elevation from the observer to the top of the tree is 25 degrees, what is the distance of the observer from the tree?",
      "Answer": 214.451
     },
     {
      "Question": "A helicopter is 800ft in air. If the distance from the point on the ground directly below the helicopter to a landing pad is known to be 373ft, what is the angle of depression to the landing pad?",
      "Answer": 25
     },
     {
      "Question": "SImon bought a new shop and wants to order a sign for the roof. From where he stands, the angle of elevation to the top of the sign is 30 degrees and the angle of elevation to the bottom of the sign is 20 degrees. Simon is standing 40 feet from the building. How tall is the sign?",
      "Answer": 8.535
     },
     {
      "Question": "From the top of a lighthouse that sits 194 meters above the sea, the angle of depression of a boat is 24. How far from the boat is the top of the lighthouse?",
      "Answer": 476.967
     },
     {
      "Question": "A plane has travelled 31 miles on an unknown heading. The plane has travelled 19 miles north. What heading east of north is the plane heading?",
      "Answer": 37.8
     },
     {
      "Question": "A semi-driver wants to know the angle of elevation of a ramp. They know it is 250 feet long and 25 feet high. What is the angle of elevation of the ramp?",
      "Answer": 5.711
     },
     {
      "Question": "If a treadmill is 30 inches long and is set to an incline of 12 degrees, how much higher is the front of the treadmill than the back?",
      "Answer": 6.237
     },
     {
      "Question": "On a windy day, a rope tightly secures a hot air balloon to a stake in the ground. From the balloon, the angle of depression to the stake is 64 degrees. The balloon is at a height of 48 feet. What is the length of the rope securing the balloon",
      "Answer": 53.405
     },
     {
      "Question": "A ladder reaches 20.5 meters up a building and makes an angle of 40 degrees with the side of the building. What is the length of the ladder?",
      "Answer": 26.761
     },
     {
      "Question": "From the top of a lighthouse that sits 97 meters above the sea, the angle of depression of a boat is 16. How far from the boat is the top of the lighthouse?",
      "Answer": 351.912
     },
     {
      "Question": "Clare is playing her favorite game of baseball while she hits a ball straight into the dirt. She hit the ball 4 feet above home plate and the ball hit the dirt 50 feet away from her. What was the angle of depression of the ball?",
      "Answer": 4.574
     },
     {
      "Question": "From the hay loft door, a farmer sees his dog on the ground. The farmer's eye level is 20.5 feet above the ground. The dog is 39 feet from the open barn door directly below the farmer. What is the angle of depression from the farmer to the dog?",
      "Answer": 27.728
     },
     {
      "Question": "From the top of a lighthouse that sits 85 meters above the sea, the angle of depression of a boat is 23. How far from the boat is the top of the lighthouse?",
      "Answer": 217.541
     },
     {
      "Question": "On a windy day, a rope tightly secures a hot air balloon to a stake in the ground. From the balloon, the angle of depression to the stake is 53 degrees. The balloon is at a height of 103 feet. What is the length of the rope securing the balloon",
      "Answer": 128.97
     },
     {
      "Question": "A helicopter is 250ft in the air. If the distance from the point on the ground directly below the helicopter on the ground to a landing pad is known to be 250ft, what is the angle of depression to the landing pad?",
      "Answer": 45
     },
     {
      "Question": "After finding that the angle of elevation to a bungee jump platform is 72 degrees, you decide to calculate how far from the platform you are. Given that the platform is 477ft tall, what is the distance to the base of the platform?",
      "Answer": 155
     },
     {
      "Question": "Clare is playing her favorite game of baseball while she hits a ball straight into the dirt. She hit the ball 6 feet above home plate and the ball hit the dirt 74 feet away from her. What was the angle of depression of the ball?",
      "Answer": 4.635
     },
     {
      "Question": "A lifeguard is at the top of tower that is 17 feet tall. The angle of depression from the lifeguard to a swimmer in the pool is 25 degrees. What is the distance from the base of the tower to the swimmer?",
      "Answer": 36.457
     },
     {
      "Question": "From the top of a lighthouse that sits 150 meters above the sea, the distance to a boat is 207 meters. What is the angle of depression to the boat?",
      "Answer": 46.439
     },
     {
      "Question": "A lighthouse built at sea level is 42 meters tall. From a buoy the angle of elevation to the top of the lighthouse is 32 degrees. How far is the buoy from the foot of the lighthouse?",
      "Answer": 67.214
     },
     {
      "Question": "If a treadmill is 38 inches long and the front is 3 inches higher than the back of the treadmill. What angle is the treadmill inclined at?",
      "Answer": 4.528
     },
     {
      "Question": "While running his favorite cross-country course, Eddie reaches the hardest part, a hill that is 3100 feet long. The hill has an incline of 12 degrees. How much elevation did Eddie gain?",
      "Answer": 644.526
     },
     {
      "Question": "SImon bought a new shop and wants to order a sign for the roof. From where he stands, the angle of elevation to the top of the sign is 40 degrees and the angle of elevation to the bottom of the sign is 22 degrees. Simon is standing 32 feet from the building. How tall is the sign?",
      "Answer": 13.922
     },
     {
      "Question": "A helicopter that is 600ft in the air measures the angle of depression to a\nlanding pad as 31 degrees. How far is the landing pad from the point directly beneath the helicopterâ€™s current position on the ground?\n",
      "Answer": 360.516
     },
     {
      "Question": "SImon bought a new shop and wants to order a sign for the roof. From where he stands, the angle of elevation to the top of the sign is 40 degrees and the angle of elevation to the bottom of the sign is 30 degrees. Simon is standing 30 feet from the building. How tall is the sign?",
      "Answer": 11.184
     },
     {
      "Question": "On a windy day, a rope tightly secures a hot air balloon to a stake in the ground. From the balloon, the angle of depression to the stake is 49 degrees. The balloon is at a height of 92 feet. What is the length of the rope securing the balloon",
      "Answer": 121.901
     },
     {
      "Question": "On a windy day, a 90 foot rope tightly secures a hot air balloon to a stake in the ground. The balloon is at a height of 79.465 feet. What is the angle of depression from the balloon to the stake in the ground?",
      "Answer": 62
     },
     {
      "Question": "Joe just got a new car, and he wants to ride it to the top of a mountain and visit a lookout point. He drives 13000 meters along a road and ends up 5287.576 meters above his starting point when he arrives at the lookout point. What is the angle of elevation of the road?",
      "Answer": 24
     },
     {
      "Question": "A plane has travelled 42 miles on an unknown heading. The plane has travelled 40 miles north. What heading east of north is the plane heading?",
      "Answer": 72.247
     },
     {
      "Question": "A man sits on a balcony next to a building 150 feet away. The angle of elevation to the top is 25 degrees and the angle of depression to the bottom is 12 degrees. How tall is the building?",
      "Answer": 101.83
     },
     {
      "Question": "A lighthouse built at sea level is 35 meters tall. The buoy is 120 meters from the base of the lighthouse. What is the angle of elevation from the buoy to the top of the lighthouse?",
      "Answer": 16.26
     },
     {
      "Question": "A semi-driver wants to know the angle of elevation of a ramp. They know it is 200 feet long and 10 feet high. What is the angle of elevation of the ramp?",
      "Answer": 2.862
     },
     {
      "Question": "A semi-driver wants to know the height of a ramp. They know it is 250 ft long and the angle of elevation is 6 degrees. What is the height of the ramp?",
      "Answer": 26.276
     },
     {
      "Question": "A ladder 18 meters long makes an angle of 20 degrees with the side of a building. How far up the building does the ladder reach?",
      "Answer": 16.914
     },
     {
      "Question": "A lighthouse built at sea level is 28 meters tall. From a buoy the angle of elevation to the top of the lighthouse is 55 degrees. How far is the buoy from the foot of the lighthouse?",
      "Answer": 19.606
     },
     {
      "Question": "A ladder reaches 15 meters up a building and makes an angle of 25 degrees with the side of the building. What is the length of the ladder?",
      "Answer": 16.551
     },
     {
      "Question": "A ladder 20 meters long makes an angle of 25 degrees with the side of a building. How far up the building does the ladder reach?",
      "Answer": 18.126
     },
     {
      "Question": "Pacing off 150 ft. on flat ground from the base of a tree which measures 126 ft in height. What is the angle of elevation to the top of the tree?",
      "Answer": 40
     },
     {
      "Question": "A lighthouse built at sea level is 25 meters tall. The buoy is 80 meters from the base of the lighthouse. What is the angle of elevation from the buoy to the top of the lighthouse?",
      "Answer": 17.354
     },
     {
      "Question": "A tree casts a shadow measuring 204ft with an angle of elevation to the sun of 32 degrees. Given this information, what is the height of the tree?",
      "Answer": 127.473
     },
     {
      "Question": "A forester measures the angle of elevation to the top of a tree as 40 degrees. If the forester knows the height of the tree to be 189ft, what distance have they paced from the tree?",
      "Answer": 225
     },
     {
      "Question": "Edward just got a new car, and he wants to ride it to the top of a mountain and visit a lookout point. He drives 11000 meters along a road and ends up 1400 meters above his starting point when he arrives at the lookout point. What is the angle of elevation of the road?",
      "Answer": 7.312
     },
     {
      "Question": "A 203ft tall tree casts a shadow of an unknown length. If the angle of elevation to the sun is 54 degrees, what is the length of the shadow?",
      "Answer": 147.488
     },
     {
      "Question": "A man sits on a balcony next to a building 167 feet away. The angle of elevation to the top is 8 degrees and the angle of depression to the bottom is 29 degrees. How tall is the building?",
      "Answer": 116.039
     },
     {
      "Question": "A man sits on a balcony next to a building 412 feet away. The angle of elevation to the top is 22 degrees and the angle of depression to the bottom is 22 degrees. How tall is the building?",
      "Answer": 332.918
     },
     {
      "Question": "From the hay loft door, a farmer sees his dog on the ground. The angle of depression to the dog is 41 degrees. The farmer's eye level is 14 feet above the ground. How many feet must the dog walk to reach the barn door directly below the farmer?",
      "Answer": 12.17
     },
     {
      "Question": "Chad just got a new car, and he wants to ride it to the top of a mountain and visit a lookout point. If he drives 8720 meters along a road that is inclined 11 degrees to the horizontal, how high above his starting point is he when he arrives at the lookout?",
      "Answer": 1663.854
     },
     {
      "Question": "If a treadmill is 48 inches long and is set to an incline of 10 degrees. How much higher is the front of the treadmill than the back?",
      "Answer": 8.335
     },
     {
      "Question": "From the hay loft door, a farmer sees his dog on the ground. The angle of depression to the dog is 40 degrees. The farmer's eye level is 16 feet above the ground. How many feet must the dog walk to reach the barn door directly below the farmer?",
      "Answer": 19.068
     },
     {
      "Question": "A lighthouse built at sea level is 28 meters tall. The buoy is 52 meters from the base of the lighthouse. What is the angle of elevation from the buoy to the top of the lighthouse?",
      "Answer": 28.301
     },
     {
      "Question": "From the top of a lighthouse that sits 105 meters above the sea, the angle of depression of a boat is 20. How far from the boat is the top of the lighthouse?",
      "Answer": 306.999
     },
     {
      "Question": "Pacing on flat ground from the base of a tree which measures 150ft in height. If the angle of elevation from the observer to the top of the tree is 60 degrees, what is the distance of the observer from the tree?",
      "Answer": 86.603
     },
     {
      "Question": "A lifeguard is at the top of tower that is 10 feet tall. The angle of depression from the lifeguard to a swimmer in the pool is 50 degrees. What is the distance from the base of the tower to the swimmer?",
      "Answer": 8.391
     },
     {
      "Question": "A 100ft tall tree casts a shadow that is 135ft long. What is the angle of elevation to the sun?",
      "Answer": 36.529
     },
     {
      "Question": "From the top of a lighthouse that sits 110 meters above the sea, the angle of depression of a boat is 50. How far from the boat is the top of the lighthouse?",
      "Answer": 143.595
     },
     {
      "Question": "A semi-driver wants to know the length of a ramp. They know it is 20 ft high and the angle of elevation is 2.862 degrees. What is the length of the ramp",
      "Answer": 400
     },
     {
      "Question": "A man sits of a balcony next to a building 300 ft away. The angle of depression to the bottom is 21 degrees and the height of the building is 288.364 ft. What is the angle of elevation to the top of the building?",
      "Answer": 30
     },
     {
      "Question": "Dillon just got a new car, and he wants to ride it to the top of a mountain and visit a lookout point. He drives 10250 meters along a road and ends up 1950 meters above his starting point when he arrives at the lookout point. What is the angle of elevation of the road?",
      "Answer": 10.967
     },
     {
      "Question": "If the distance from the point directly below a helicopter on the ground to a landing pad is known to be 200ft and the angle of depression to the landing pad is 33 degrees, what is the current altitude of the helicopter?",
      "Answer": 307.973
     },
     {
      "Question": "You are standing 124 ft from the base of a bungee jump platform. If the angle of elevation to the platform is 65 degrees, what is the height of the platform?",
      "Answer": 265.919
     },
     {
      "Question": "From the top of a lighthouse that sits 194 meters above the sea, the angle of depression of a boat is 16. How far from the boat is the top of the lighthouse?",
      "Answer": 702.898
     },
     {
      "Question": "A semi-driver wants to know the height of a ramp. They know it is 400 ft long and the angle of elevation is 2.862 degrees. What is the height of the ramp?",
      "Answer": 20
     },
     {
      "Question": "From the top of a lighthouse that sits 150 meters above the sea, the distance to a boat is 219 meters. What is the angle of depression to the boat?",
      "Answer": 43.23
     },
     {
      "Question": "A ladder 22 meters long makes an angle of 17 degrees with the side of a building. How far up the building does the ladder reach?",
      "Answer": 21.039
     },
     {
      "Question": "A ladder 19 meters long makes an angle of 22 degrees with the side of a building. How far up the building does the ladder reach?",
      "Answer": 17.616
     },
     {
      "Question": "Pacing off 150ft. on flat ground from the base of a tree which measures 179ft in height. What is the angle of elevation to the top of the tree?",
      "Answer": 40
     },
     {
      "Question": "From the hay loft door, a farmer sees his dog on the ground. The angle of depression to the dog is 64 degrees. The farmer's eye level is 12 feet above the ground. How many feet must the dog walk to reach the barn door directly below the farmer?",
      "Answer": 24.604
     },
     {
      "Question": "From the hay loft door, a farmer sees his dog on the ground. The farmer's eye level is 19.5 feet above the ground. The dog is 41 feet from the open barn door directly below the farmer. What is the angle of depression from the farmer to the dog?",
      "Answer": 22.436
     },
     {
      "Question": "Pacing on flat ground from the base of a tree which measures 300ft in height. If the angle of elevation from the observer to the top of the tree is 72 degrees, what is the distance of the observer from the tree?",
      "Answer": 97.476
     },
     {
      "Question": "Clare is playing her favorite game of baseball while she hits a ball straight into the dirt. She hit the ball 6.5 feet above home plate and the ball hit the dirt 100 feet away from her. What was the angle of depression of the ball?",
      "Answer": 3.719
     },
     {
      "Question": "A plane has travelled 27 miles on an unknown heading. The plane has travelled 22 miles north. What heading east of north is the plane heading?",
      "Answer": 54.569
     },
     {
      "Question": "A man sits on a balcony next to a building 300 feet away. The angle of elevation to the top is 30 degrees and the angle of depression to the bottom is 21 degrees. How tall is the building?",
      "Answer": 288.364
     },
     {
      "Question": "A lighthouse built at sea level. From a buoy the angle of elevation to the top of the lighthouse is 35 degrees. The buoy is 57.126 meters from the base of the lighthouse. What is the height of the lighthouse?",
      "Answer": 40
     },
     {
      "Question": "While waiting for your sister to finish her bungee jump, you decide to figure out the angle of elevation to the top of the platform. You know the platform is 181ft tall and you are 361ft from the platform. What is the angle of elevation to the platform?",
      "Answer": 26.629
     },
     {
      "Question": "Pacing off 80ft. on flat ground from the base of a tree which measures 140ft in height. What is the angle of elevation to the top of the tree?",
      "Answer": 60.255
     },
     {
      "Question": "On a windy day, a 82 foot rope tightly secures a hot air balloon to a stake in the ground. From the balloon, the angle of depression to the stake is 42 degrees. What is the height of the balloon",
      "Answer": 54.869
     },
     {
      "Question": "A ladder 20 meters long reaches 18.126 meters up the side of a building. What angle does the ladder form with the side of the building?",
      "Answer": 25
     },
     {
      "Question": "A lighthouse built at sea level is 40 meters tall. From a buoy the angle of elevation to the top of the lighthouse is 35 degrees. How far is the buoy from the foot of the lighthouse?",
      "Answer": 57.126
     },
     {
      "Question": "While waiting for your sister to finish her bungee jump, you decide to figure out the angle of elevation to the top of the platform. You know the platform is 381ft tall and you are 323ft from the platform. What is the angle of elevation to the platform?",
      "Answer": 49.71
     },
     {
      "Question": "A 153ft tall tree casts a shadow of an unknown length. If the angle of elevation to the sun is 30 degrees, what is the length of the shadow?",
      "Answer": 265.004
     },
     {
      "Question": "A semi-driver wants to know the height of a ramp. They know it is 325 ft long and the angle of elevation is 9 degrees. What is the height of the ramp?",
      "Answer": 51.475
     },
     {
      "Question": "A forester measures the angle of elevation to the top of a tree as 40 degress. What is the height of that tree if the forester paced 150ft away on flat ground?",
      "Answer": 125.865
     },
     {
      "Question": "A 88ft tall tree casts a shadow that is 135ft long. What is the angle of elevation to the sun?",
      "Answer": 33.02
     },
     {
      "Question": "A helicopter that is 500ft in the air measures the angle of depression to a\nlanding pad as 50 degrees. How far is the landing pad from the point directly beneath the helicopterâ€™s current position on the ground?\n",
      "Answer": 595.877
     },
     {
      "Question": "A lighthouse built at sea level is 32 meters tall. From a buoy the angle of elevation to the top of the lighthouse is 35 degrees. How far is the buoy from the foot of the lighthouse?",
      "Answer": 45.701
     },
     {
      "Question": "While waiting for your sister to finish her bungee jump, you decide to figure out the angle of elevation to the top of the platform. You know the platform is 477ft tall and you are 155ft from the platform. What is the angle of elevation to the platform?",
      "Answer": 72
     },
     {
      "Question": "A ladder reaches 18.126 meters up a building and makes an angle of 25 degrees with the side of the building. What is the length of the ladder?",
      "Answer": 20
     },
     {
      "Question": "On a windy day, a 27 foot rope tightly secures a hot air balloon to a stake in the ground. From the balloon, the angle of depression to the stake is 63 degrees. What is the height of the balloon",
      "Answer": 24.057
     },
     {
      "Question": "A man sits on a balcony next to a building 177 feet away. The angle of elevation to the top is 9 degrees and the angle of depression to the bottom is 22 degrees. How tall is the building?",
      "Answer": 99.547
     },
     {
      "Question": "A tree casts a shadow measuring 101ft with an angle of elevation to the sun of 60 degrees. Given this information, what is the height of the tree?",
      "Answer": 174.937
     },
     {
      "Question": "SImon bought a new shop and wants to order a sign for the roof. From where he stands, the angle of elevation to the top of the sign is 42 degrees and the angle of elevation to the bottom of the sign is 31 degrees. Simon is standing 24 feet from the building. How tall is the sign?",
      "Answer": 7.189
     },
     {
      "Question": "If a treadmill is 42 inches long and is set to an incline of 9 degrees, how much higher is the front of the treadmill than the back?",
      "Answer": 6.57
     },
     {
      "Question": "A tree casts a shadow measuring 114ft with an angle of elevation to the sun of 52 degrees. Given this information, what is the height of the tree?",
      "Answer": 145.913
     },
     {
      "Question": "A lifeguard is at the top of tower that is 18 feet tall. The angle of depression from the lifeguard to a swimmer in the pool is 15 degrees. What is the distance from the base of the tower to the swimmer?",
      "Answer": 67.177
     },
     {
      "Question": "A man sits of a balcony next to a building 300 ft away. The angle of elevation to the top is 30 degrees and the height of the building is 288.364 ft. What is the angle of depression to the bottom of the building?",
      "Answer": 21
     },
     {
      "Question": "If a treadmill is 24 inches long and is set to an incline of 10 degrees, how much higher is the front of the treadmill than the back?",
      "Answer": 4.168
     },
     {
      "Question": "A lifeguard is at the top of tower that is 12 feet tall. The angle of depression from the lifeguard to a swimmer in the pool is 60 degrees. What is the distance from the base of the tower to the swimmer?",
      "Answer": 6.928
     },
     {
      "Question": "If a treadmill is 30 inches long and the front is 5 inches higher than the back of the treadmill. What angle is the treadmill inclined at?",
      "Answer": 9.594
     },
     {
      "Question": "From the hay loft door, a farmer sees his dog on the ground. The farmer's eye level is 22 feet above the ground. The dog is 47 feet from the open barn door directly below the farmer. What is the angle of depression from the farmer to the dog?",
      "Answer": 25.084
     },
     {
      "Question": "From the hay loft door, a farmer sees his dog on the ground. The angle of depression to the dog is 66 degrees. The farmer's eye level is 17 feet above the ground. How many feet must the dog walk to reach the barn door directly below the farmer?",
      "Answer": 38.183
     },
     {
      "Question": "A man sits on a balcony next to a building 500 feet away. The angle of elevation to the top is 7 degrees and the angle of depression to the bottom is 34 degrees. How tall is the building?",
      "Answer": 398.647
     },
     {
      "Question": "The distance to a boat from the top of lighthouse is 351 meters. If the height of the lighthouse is 97 meters, what is the angle of depression to the boat?",
      "Answer": 16
     },
     {
      "Question": "On a windy day, a rope tightly secures a hot air balloon to a stake in the ground. From the balloon, the angle of depression to the stake is 57 degrees. The balloon is at a height of 79 feet. What is the length of the rope securing the balloon",
      "Answer": 94.197
     },
     {
      "Question": "Clare is playing her favorite game of baseball while she hits a ball straight into the dirt. She hit the ball with an angle of depression of 7 degrees and the ball hit the dirt 78 feet away from her. How high above the home plate was the ball when hit?",
      "Answer": 9.577
     },
     {
      "Question": "Allie just got a new car, and she wants to ride it to the top of a mountain and visit a lookout point. If she drives 11650 meters along a road that is inclined 9 degrees to the horizontal, how high above her starting point is she when she arrives at the lookout?",
      "Answer": 1822.462
     },
     {
      "Question": "If a treadmill is 32 inches long and is set to an incline of 10 degrees, how much higher is the front of the treadmill than the back?",
      "Answer": 5.557
     },
     {
      "Question": "From the top of a lighthouse that sits 97 meters above the sea, the distance to a boat is 351 meters. What is the angle of depression to the boat?",
      "Answer": 16
     },
     {
      "Question": "A ladder reaches 17 meters up a building and makes an angle of 19 degrees with the side of the building. What is the length of the ladder?",
      "Answer": 17.98
     },
     {
      "Question": "SImon bought a new shop and wants to order a sign for the roof. From where he stands, the distance to the building is 27 feet. The height from the top of the sign is 37 feet. What is the angle of elevation to the top of the sign?",
      "Answer": 36.119
     },
     {
      "Question": "A lifeguard is at the top of tower that is 22 feet tall. The base of the tower is 80 feet away from a swimmer in the pool. What is the angle of depression from the lifeguard to the swimmer?",
      "Answer": 15.376
     },
     {
      "Question": "A plane has travelled 22 miles on an unknown heading. The plane has travelled 20 miles north. What heading east of north is the plane heading?",
      "Answer": 65.38
     },
     {
      "Question": "A semi-driver wants to know the height of a ramp. They know it is 300 ft long and the angle of elevation is 7 degrees. What is the height of the ramp?",
      "Answer": 36.835
     },
     {
      "Question": "Phineas just got a new car, and he wants to ride it to the top of a mountain and visit a lookout point. If he drives 9450 meters along a road that is inclined 20 degrees to the horizontal, how high above his starting point is he when he arrives at the lookout?",
      "Answer": 3232.09
     },
     {
      "Question": "While running his favorite cross-country course, Eddie reaches the hardest part, a hill that has an incline of 7 degrees. Eddie gains 950 feet in elevation at the top. What is the length of hill?",
      "Answer": 7795.234
     },
     {
      "Question": "While waiting for your sister to finish her bungee jump, you decide to figure out how you are from the platform. You know the platform is 477ft tall and the angle of elevation from you to the top of the platform is 72 degrees. How far from the platform are you?",
      "Answer": 155
     },
     {
      "Question": "A lifeguard is at the top of tower that is 15 feet tall. The angle of depression from the lifeguard to a swimmer in the pool is 35 degrees. What is the distance from the base of the tower to the swimmer?",
      "Answer": 21.422
     },
     {
      "Question": "Pacing off 300 ft. on flat ground from the base of a tree, a forester measures the\nangle of elevation to the top of the tree as 32 degrees. What is the height of the tree?",
      "Answer": 187.461
     },
     {
      "Question": "Clare is playing her favorite game of baseball while she hits a ball straight into the dirt. She hit the ball 5 feet above home plate and the ball hit the dirt 59 feet away from her. What was the angle of depression of the ball?",
      "Answer": 4.844
     },
     {
      "Question": "SImon bought a new shop and wants to order a sign for the roof. From where he stands, the angle of elevation to the top of the sign is 34 degrees and the angle of elevation to the bottom of the sign is 16 degrees. Simon is standing 44 feet from the building. How tall is the sign?",
      "Answer": 17.062
     },
     {
      "Question": "From the top of a lighthouse that sits 200 meters above the sea, the angle of depression of a boat is 45 degrees. How far from the boat is the top of the lighthouse?",
      "Answer": 282.843
     },
     {
      "Question": "A ladder 10 meters long makes an angle of 12 degrees with the side of a building. How far up the building does the ladder reach?",
      "Answer": 9.781
     },
     {
      "Question": "On a windy day, a 43 foot rope tightly secures a hot air balloon to a stake in the ground. From the balloon, the angle of depression to the stake is 57 degrees. What is the height of the balloon",
      "Answer": 36.063
     },
     {
      "Question": "A ladder reaches 21 meters up a building and makes an angle of 31 degrees with the side of the building. What is the length of the ladder?",
      "Answer": 24.499
     },
     {
      "Question": "From the hay loft door, a farmer sees his dog on the ground. The angle of depression to the dog is 57 degrees. The farmer's eye level is 20 feet above the ground. How many feet must the dog walk to reach the barn door directly below the farmer?",
      "Answer": 30.797
     },
     {
      "Question": "A lighthouse built at sea level is 30 meters tall. The buoy is 40 meters from the base of the lighthouse. What is the angle of elevation from the buoy to the top of the lighthouse?",
      "Answer": 36.87
     },
     {
      "Question": "While running his favorite cross-country course, Eddie reaches the hardest part, a hill that is 4250 feet long. The hill has an incline of 20 degrees. How much elevation did Eddie gain?",
      "Answer": 1453.586
     },
     {
      "Question": "From the hay loft door, a farmer sees his dog on the ground. The angle of depression to the dog is 52 degrees. The farmer's eye level is 13.5 feet above the ground. How many feet must the dog walk to reach the barn door directly below the farmer?",
      "Answer": 17.279
     },
     {
      "Question": "If a treadmill is 32 inches long and the front is 6 inches higher than the back of the treadmill. What angle is the treadmill inclined at?",
      "Answer": 10.807
     },
     {
      "Question": "A plane has travelled 24 miles on an unknown heading. The plane has travelled 15 miles north. What heading east of north is the plane heading?",
      "Answer": 38.682
     },
     {
      "Question": "Clare is playing her favorite game of baseball while she hits a ball straight into the dirt. She hit the ball with an angle of depression of 7 degrees and the ball hit the dirt 100 feet away from her. How high above the home plate was the ball when hit?",
      "Answer": 12.278
     },
     {
      "Question": "A tree casts a shadow measuring 87ft with an angle of elevation to the sun of 25 degrees. Given this information, what is the height of the tree?",
      "Answer": 40.569
     },
     {
      "Question": "While running his favorite cross-country course, Eddie reaches the hardest part, a hill that has an incline of 8 degrees. Eddie gains 1200 feet in elevation at the top. What is the length of hill?",
      "Answer": 8622.356
     },
     {
      "Question": "A lifeguard is at the top of tower that is 19 feet tall. The base of the tower is 45 feet away from a swimmer in the pool. What is the angle of depression from the lifeguard to the swimmer?",
      "Answer": 22.891
     },
     {
      "Question": "A lifeguard is at the top of tower that is 18 feet tall. The base of the tower is 57 feet away from a swimmer in the pool. What is the angle of depression from the lifeguard to the swimmer?",
      "Answer": 17.526
     },
     {
      "Question": "From the hay loft door, a farmer sees his dog on the ground. The farmer's eye level is 19 feet above the ground. The dog is 52 feet from the open barn door directly below the farmer. What is the angle of depression from the farmer to the dog?",
      "Answer": 20.072
     },
     {
      "Question": "Jugal just got a new car, and he wants to ride it to the top of a mountain and visit a lookout point. If he drives 12430 meters along a road that is inclined 10 degrees to the horizontal, how high above his starting point is he when he arrives at the lookout?",
      "Answer": 2158.447
     },
     {
      "Question": "From the top of a lighthouse that sits 115 meters above the sea, the angle of depression of a boat is 60. How far from the boat is the top of the lighthouse?",
      "Answer": 132.791
     },
     {
      "Question": "Find the length of a shadow cast by a tree known to be 176ft tall assuming the angle of elevation to the sun is 33 degrees.",
      "Answer": 270
     },
     {
      "Question": "A 176ft tall tree casts a shadow of an unknown length. If the angle of elevation to the sun is 33 degrees, what is the length of the shadow?",
      "Answer": 270
     },
     {
      "Question": "If a treadmill is set to an incline of 10 degrees and the front is 8.335 inches higher than the back of the treadmill. What is the length of the treadmill?",
      "Answer": 48
     },
     {
      "Question": "While waiting for your sister to finish her bungee jump, you decide to figure out how you are from the platform. You know the platform is 243ft tall and the angle of elevation from you to the top of the platform is 45 degrees. How far from the platform are you?",
      "Answer": 243
     },
     {
      "Question": "Clare is playing her favorite game of baseball while she hits a ball straight into the dirt. She hit the ball with an angle of depression of 8 degrees and the ball hit the dirt 92 feet away from her. How high above the home plate was the ball when hit?",
      "Answer": 12.93
     },
     {
      "Question": "On a windy day, a 57 foot rope tightly secures a hot air balloon to a stake in the ground. From the balloon, the angle of depression to the stake is 37 degrees. What is the height of the balloon",
      "Answer": 34.303
     },
     {
      "Question": "A plane has traveled 49 miles on a course heading 42 degrees east of north. How far north has the plane travelled at this point?",
      "Answer": 36.414
     },
     {
      "Question": "Clare is playing her favorite game of baseball while she hits a ball straight into the dirt. She hit the ball 4 feet above home plate and the angle of depression of the ball was 4.574 degrees. How far from the plate did the ball hit the dirt?",
      "Answer": 50
     },
     {
      "Question": "A lighthouse built at sea level is 40 meters tall. The buoy is 150 meters from the base of the lighthouse. What is the angle of elevation from the buoy to the top of the lighthouse?",
      "Answer": 14.931
     },
     {
      "Question": "A plane has traveled 51 miles on a course heading 37 degrees east of north. How far north has the plane travelled at this point?",
      "Answer": 40.73
     },
     {
      "Question": "From the top of a lighthouse that sits 180 meters above the sea, the distance to a boat is 197 meters. What is the angle of depression to the boat?",
      "Answer": 66.023
     },
     {
      "Question": "Clare is playing her favorite game of baseball while she hits a ball straight into the dirt. She hit the ball with an angle of depression of 6 degrees and the ball hit the dirt 73 feet away from her. How high above the home plate was the ball when hit?",
      "Answer": 7.673
     },
     {
      "Question": "A plane has traveled 26 miles on a course heading 48 degrees east of north. How far north has the plane travelled at this point?",
      "Answer": 17.397
     },
     {
      "Question": "Pacing on flat ground from the base of a tree which measures 200ft in height. If the angle of elevation from the observer to the top of the tree is 51 degrees, what is the distance of the observer from the tree?",
      "Answer": 161.957
     },
     {
      "Question": "A man sits on a balcony next to a building 324 feet away. The angle of elevation to the top is 11 degrees and the angle of depression to the bottom is 36 degrees. How tall is the building?",
      "Answer": 298.379
     },
     {
      "Question": "You are currently standing 124ft from the base of a bungee jump platform and the angle of elevation to that platform is 72 degrees. Find the height of the platform",
      "Answer": 361.633
     },
     {
      "Question": "A lighthouse built at sea level is 40 meters tall. The buoy is 57.126 meters from the base of the lighthouse. What is the angle of elevation from the buoy to the top of the lighthouse?",
      "Answer": 35
     },
     {
      "Question": "On a windy day, a 90 foot rope tightly secures a hot air balloon to a stake in the ground. From the balloon, the angle of depression to the stake is 62 degrees. What is the height of the balloon",
      "Answer": 79.465
     },
     {
      "Question": "Rick just got a new car, and he wants to ride it to the top of a mountain and visit a lookout point. He drives 12500 meters along a road and ends up 3200 meters above his starting point when he arrives at the lookout point. What is the angle of elevation of the road?",
      "Answer": 14.833
     },
     {
      "Question": "Clare is playing her favorite game of baseball while she hits a ball straight into the dirt. She hit the ball 5.5 feet above home plate and the ball hit the dirt 82 feet away from her. What was the angle of depression of the ball?",
      "Answer": 3.837
     },
     {
      "Question": "A helicopter that is 400ft in the air measures the angle of depression to a\nlanding pad as 55 degrees. How far is the landing pad from the point directly beneath the helicopterâ€™s current position on the ground?\n",
      "Answer": 642.667
     },
     {
      "Question": "On a windy day, a rope tightly secures a hot air balloon to a stake in the ground. From the balloon, the angle of depression to the stake is 37 degrees. The balloon is at a height of 45 feet. What is the length of the rope securing the balloon",
      "Answer": 74.774
     },
     {
      "Question": "Olivia just got a new car, and she wants to ride it to the top of a mountain and visit a lookout point. If she drives 10900 meters along a road that is inclined 8 degrees to the horizontal, how high above her starting point is he when she arrives at the lookout?",
      "Answer": 1516.987
     },
     {
      "Question": "SImon bought a new shop and wants to order a sign for the roof. From where he stands, the angle of elevation to the top of the sign is 45 degrees and the angle of elevation to the bottom of the sign is 19 degrees. Simon is standing 22 feet from the building. How tall is the sign?",
      "Answer": 14.425
     },
     {
      "Question": "A man sits on a balcony next to a building 343 feet away. The angle of elevation to the top is 23 degrees and the angle of depression to the bottom is 21 degrees. How tall is the building?",
      "Answer": 277.26
     },
     {
      "Question": "Sophie is skiing down a hill. She is going at a fast speed of 36 miles per hour for 2 minutes. If the slope had an incline of 35 degrees, how much elevation did she drop in feet?",
      "Answer": 3634.18
     }
]
    